Guide to the Records of the Tisch School of the Arts 1956-1981 (Bulk 1965-1981) RG 35
New York University Archives
- ACCESSION 93-025
  - Series V: Administrative Files
    - Telephones, Analysis of Toll Calls, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Television - Cable + Alternate Media Center, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Television - Fox International Conference Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Theatre Program, Jan 1975-Mar 1976 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Theatre Program, Apr 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Theatre Program, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Theatre Program, Admissions and Auditions, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226093 8
    - Theatre Program - memos, D.Oppenheim/D. DeMers; DeMers/Oppenheim; DeMers/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Theatre Program - memos, D.Oppenheim/ D. Demers; DeMers/ Oppenheim; DeMers/anyone, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Program, Productions, Karen DeFrancis, Co-ord., 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - The Village, The Village, film, J. Cohen, S. Rosenberg, 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Time Sheets, D. Oppenheim's Office, 1976-1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Turell, Prof. Saul, "Producing for Film" (undergrad course), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Undergrad. Admissions Publications, Task Force to Review, (incl. General Ed. Conf. 4/22/77), 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Undergrad. Ed. Study, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Von Raab, William, V.P. Administration, memos, 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - W - General, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - W - General, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - WNCN, Classical Music Station, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - WNCN, Classical Music Station, "Petition for Revocation of License...", Sep 1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Young Audiences, incl. By-Laws, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Young Audiences, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Young Audiences, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Young Audiences, Reports, Guidelines, Promo Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Subseries A: Administrative Files, con't.
      - Grad. Committee Proposals, ca.1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226578 8
      - Hamerow, Eleanor, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Hammerstein, Dorothy, 1983-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Hodes, Roberta, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Hodes, Roberta: Tenure, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Hodes, Stuart, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Hamberger, Barnett W., 1979-1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Horowitz, Helen, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Huntley, Chet, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Ad Hoc Committee for Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Interschool Committee on Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Interschool Committee on Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Interschool Committee on Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Interschool Committee on Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Interschool Committee on Undergrad Education, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Jaffe, Pat, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226579 6
      - Jaffe, Pat: Tenure, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Jaffe, Leo: Dinner, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Jaffe, Toby, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Johnson: Candidate Submissions, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Johnson: Candidate Submissions, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Kaufman, George, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Lake Systems, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - League, 1982-1985 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Legal Counsel, 1983-1985 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Londino, Harry, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Levine, Harry, 1982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Levine, Naomi, 1985-1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - A-File, 1970-1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226580 4
      - Admissions: NYU Office of Director - Harold R. Doughty, 1976-1980 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Advertising: SOA - Jill Abrandt-J. Mongelli, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Advertising: SOA - Jill Abrandt-J. Mongelli, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Alternate Media Center, 1972-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - SOA Annual Report: Drafts, Originals, Copies, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - NYU Program: Art in Venice, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - B-File, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Design Department Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Summer Statistics, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Fichandler, Zelda, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226581 2
      - Fichandler, Zelda, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Fichandler, Zelda, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Film Festival (SOA), 1981 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Financial Aid, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Financial Aid, 1982-1984 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Financial Aid: Funded, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Financial Aid: Recipients, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Five Year Plan: College of Arts and Science, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Foreign Students Committee, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Frankfurt, Stephen O.: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Friars, 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - French Revolution: Bicentennial, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Friedkin, William, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226582 0
      - Fundraising, SOA, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Gallatin Division, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Gallatin Fellows (also Medalists), undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Gitlow, Abraham, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Gerbarg, Darcy, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Goddard, Paulette, 1977-1986 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Goddard, Paulette, 1978-1983 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Carter, Donald, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226583 8
      - Cantor, Norman, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Challenge Grants: NEA, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Challenge Grants: Material, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Claxton, Alex, 1982-1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Costello, Robert, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Cost Allocations, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Cost Allocations, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Committees (Standing), 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Cooper, Roberta, 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Course Information Sheets: SOA Departments, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Deans Council (Oppenheim - Chairman), 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Alternate Media Center Proposal, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226584 6
      - Alternate Media Center, 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Cinema Studies, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Cinema Studies, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Cinema Studies, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Cinema Studies, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - UG Drama, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - UG Drama, 1980-1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Dramatic Writing, 1981-1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Search Committee Chair: Dramatic Writing, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - DWP: Evaluations, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - DWP: Admissions, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - DWP: Budget, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - DWP: Related Correspondence, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Town Hall, 1982-1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226585 3
      - Town Hall: Young Artists Series, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Town Hall: Young Artists Series - Miscellaneous Materials, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Weiler, Alan, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Wilson, Richard: NYU Insurance, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Winston, Brian, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Winston, Brian, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Workshops, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Workstudy Information, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Wreen, Peggy, 1987-1989 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Yearbook, TSOA, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Young Audiences, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Academy of Motion Picture, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226586 1
      - Alumni Federation, 1977-1981 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Actors and Directors Lab, 1977-1979 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Ad Hoc Committee: Adler, Stella, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Advertising, 1977-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Administration for VP, 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Alumni Gift/ABC/Amer. Ctr. Paris: Mrs. G. Amberg, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - American Cinematique, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Art Program Committee: SOA, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Annenberg Center: Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Attrition, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Mrs. Harry Baer: Balance of Trade, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Budget Policy Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Budget Policy Advisory Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Buildings 51 West 4th St., 1980 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Buildings 721 & 719 Broadway, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Buildings 725 Broadway, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Buildings 144 Bleecker St., undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Lloyd Burlingame, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - California Campaign, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Chernichaw, Mark: Tenure Materials, undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Theater Program: Prod. And Perf., 1979 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Theater Program: Reg., undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Photography Major Proposal, undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Musical Theater Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Acting Miscellaneous Memos, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226587 9
      - Sarah Lawrence College, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1973-1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - SOA Annual Report: Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - J.S. Seidman Theater Awards: Presentation, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - J.S. Seidman Theater Awards: Grants and Scholarships, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Shaplie, Omar, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Simonides, Yannis, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Sirota, David, undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Ad-Hoc Space Committee: SOA Summer, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Staples, Donald E., Professor: Department of Cinema Studies, 0000 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Summer Session: Fee Schedule, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Summer Session, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Theater Program, 1968-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226588 7
      - Summer Session Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Summer Session Committee: David Oppenheim, Chairman, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Switz, Mr. O. Wrightson: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - T-File+C246, 1974-1979 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - TSOA Bulletin, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Taggart, Joseph H.: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Tanis: Letters from Professionals, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Tanis: Letters from Faculty Members, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Tanis: Letters from Students, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Tenure Report: Nicholas P. Tanis, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Theater Program, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Theater Program, 1977-1979 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Theater Program Development Group, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Todman, William S.: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Wharton, Mrs. John F.: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - WNYU-FM, 1975-1979 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Milne, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226589 5
      - Milne, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Mobil Fellows, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Mobil Awards, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Mobil Awards, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Neipris, Janet, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Neipris, Janet, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Oliva, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Oliva, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Oppenheim, Dean David: Memoranda and Correspondence, Single Mailing, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Oppenheim, Dean David: Memoranda and Correspondence, Multiple Mailing, 1976-1982 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Oppenheim Multiples, 1982-1985 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Oppenheim, 1982-1984 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Oppenheim, Dean David, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226590 3
      - Oppenheim, Dean David: Personal - Non-NYU Materials, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Press, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Press, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Press, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Radio Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Sirota, David, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Sponsored Research and Training Program Manual, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Studio School, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Summer, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Summer, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Summer, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Summer, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Letters and Memos, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226594 5
      - Hoffman, Ted: Files, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Hoffman, Ted: Confidential Program Files, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Inter. Con. Fine Arts Dean's, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Johnson, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Portfolio Information Sheets, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Chris Launois: Undergraduate, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - John Coleman, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Richard Gioia, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - John McIntyre, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Adam Suarez, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Johnson, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - D.O. Notes, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - B.K. Gimblett, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - B.K. Gimblett, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Annual Reports by Dept., 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226591 1
      - SOA Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous/Drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - SOA Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - SOA Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - SOA Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - SOA Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - SOA Annual Report, 1975-1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Annual Reports by Dept., 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Annual Reports by Dept., 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Annual Reports by Dept., 1978 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Balos, Rowena P.: Faculty, Dept. of Acting, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Baruch, Sylvia, undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Bilby, Kenneth: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Bistram, Cecilia, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Departmental Operating Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Departmental Operating Budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Departmental Budget Allocations: Codes 301 (Capital Budgets), 1985 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Departmental Budget Allocations: Codes 201, 400, 407, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Budget: Procedures and Guidelines, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Departmental Operating Budgets, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Departmental Budget Allocations: Codes 201, 400, 407, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Budgets by Department: TSOA, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - TSOA Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - President's Budget Message, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226592 9
      - Budget Narrative, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - SOA Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Narrative Draft to Bing/Claxton: Delivered BPAC Comm., 1983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - SOA Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Budget: Faculty and Admin. Staff, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Budget: SOA - Extra Copies; Proposal with some attachments, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Budget Narrative, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Original Budges, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - SOA Budget by Dept., 1980 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Department Budget Meetings and Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Departmental Annual Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Budget Policy Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - BPAC, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Budget Advisory Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - BPAC, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Burlingame, 1981-1986 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Burlingame, 1981-1983 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Burns, Red, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Burns, Red, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Burns, Red, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Butler, Marshall, undated (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - TSOA Memos, undated (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Gimblett, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226593 7
      - Gimblett, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Lampert, Rachel, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Lasdon, Jeffrey, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Levine, Naomi, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Alumni Memos: Levine To and From, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Leyda, Jay: Gottesman Professor of Cinema Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Files and Mailing Lists, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Film Society Pricing, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Stuart Lyons, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Legal, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Mantel, Muriel, undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Marcus, Ann, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Marcus, Ann, 1982-1988 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Mannes College of Music, undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Mannes College of Music, undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Faculty Meetings, undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - JMM, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - JMM, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - JMM, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - B-File, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226595 2
      - Balance of Trade Committee, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Deans/Officers/President Weekly Meeting, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Benedek, Laslo: Chairman, Dept. of Film and TV Personal File, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Bennet, Ivan L.: Thank You's to SOA Donors, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Brunetti, Vito, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Budget: Memos To and From Joseph Eugene, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Budget SOA: Bing-Claxton, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Budget SOA: Bing-Claxton, 1980-1981 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Budget (Memos To and From Bing, Claxton, Hoover, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Budget Estimates, SOA, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - C-File, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Committee Lists SOA, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226596 0
      - Committees and Committee Representation, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - D-File+C476, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - DeMus, Danielle, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Department of Cinema Studies (Sklar - Chairman), 1979-1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Department of Cinema Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Department of Dance (Stuart Hodes - Chairman), 1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Department of Drama: Undergraduate, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Department of Drama: Undergraduate, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - UGFTV, 1984-1985 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226597 8
      - UGFTV, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Department of Film and TV: Charles Milne, Acting Chairman, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Graduate Film, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Evaluations (Spring), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Richard Friedman: Extras, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Grad Film: Admission Revocations: Dean's Letter to Fall Incoming Students, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Price, Heidi, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - GFTV: Admission Revocations and Deferrals, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - DiMattia, Judy: Communications Plan/Broadway Complex, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Interactive Telecommunications Program, 1981-1985 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - ITP Contracts: Course Descriptions, 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - TITP: Annenberg - Project Proposal, undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Performance Studies, 1980-1985 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Photography, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226598 6
      - Theater Program, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Theater Program, 1980-1982 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Appointments, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Theater Program: Contracts, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Theater Program: Contracts, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Department of Dance: Gary Rhodes, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Design, 1982-1985 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Design, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Directing: Alumni List, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - A: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226599 4
      - Affirmative Action, NYU (Evelynne Paterson Director), undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - American Center (Paris), undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - American Theater Wing, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Buildings Central Plaza (111 2nd Ave.), undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Charlap, Guy: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Musical Theater Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Propsal as Submitted to Grad Commission, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Directing Chair: C. Weber, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Educational Policy Committee, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Eisenstat, Jay: Memorial Commission, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Expository Writing Program, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Faculty Organization, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Faculty Organization Plan, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Faculty Organization Plan Rev. Materials, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Attachments for Standing Committee Discipline: Appendix 1-3, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Faculty Policy and Procedures Stats/Rec-80, undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Faculty Retirement (SOA), undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226600 0
      - Faculty Staffing (Confidential), undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Film Festival: Film Production Fund, 1978-1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Film Festival Awars: Ceremonny (5/22), 1978 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Film Society of Lincoln Center, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Financial Aid, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 6)